export const EnglishQuestions = [
    {
        id:'quest-1',
        question:'How much should I invest in Boosting?',
        answer:`Boosting guarantees that you only pay for the clicks that your listing gets. The cost of each campaign depends on your budget. The higher your budget, the more clicks the campaign will try to deliver to your listing. Marketoo suggests you to purchase from $0.1 - $10/ per click.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-2',
        question:'Can I pay in advance and start advertising in preferred duration?',
        answer:`Yes. You may select your preferred duration via the calendar.  Duration must be minimum 3days or maximum 30days.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-3',
        question:'Why should I pay for higher clicks?',
        answer:`Higher clicks correlate with a more prominent position when sellers share same Ad score and same Product
        Quality score, thereby delivering clicks faster for a successful campaign and competing with other sellers
        in the category in a given period of time.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-4',
        question:'If I do not pay for higher clicks, does this mean my Boosting ads will perform poorly?',
        answer:`No. Your Boosting listing will be shown in relevant search and browse results. We will still aim to deliver 100% of your daily budget. Your Boosting performance will not be impacted. Higher Clicks is built for the serious sellers who urgently want more exposure and clicks in a specific given period of the time.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-5',
        question:'What if all other sellers pay for the same clicks? Who will be prioritised?',
        answer:`If all other sellers are paying for the same clicks, then all of their listings will be prioritised based on the 
        highest Product Quality score followed by the highest Ad Score.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-6',
        question:'How do I put my listing into Boosting?',
        answer:`<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">1 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Select products from your profile;</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">2 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Look for slide bars to adjust Daily Budgets, Bid / Click Budget and days you want to advertise for.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br /></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">3 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Customise your Boosting campaign with your ideal duration and keywords. You pay then proceed to confirm payment by tapping on &ldquo;Boost Now&rdquo; </span></p>`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-7',
        question:'How do I pay for my Boosting?',
        answer:`Ads features like Boosting can be purchased via Apple Pay, Google Pay, Ali Pay, WeChat Pay, Credit Card,
        PayMe, FPS.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-8',
        question:'How do I Track the clicks and progress of your Boosting campaign?',
        answer:`Track the clicks and progress of your Boosting campaign through My Ads Performance in “Boosting”`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-9',
        question:'How to calculate Product Quality score? What is the Maximum Product Quality?',
        answer:`Your Product Quality score is calculated by (Conversation Rate + CTR) x 5.
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maximum Product Quality is 10.&nbsp;</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Note:</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">1) Clickthrough rate (CTR) can be used to gauge how well your keywords and ads, and free listings,
        are performing. CTR is the number of clicks that your ad receives divided by the number of times
        your ad is shown: clicks ÷ impressions = CTR. For example, if you had 5 clicks and 100
        impressions, then your CTR would be 5%.</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">2) The conversion rate is the number of conversions divided by the total number of visitors. For example, 
        if an e-commerce site receives 200 visitors in a month and has 50 sales, the conversion rate would be 50 
        divided by 200, or 25%.</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">3) If no sales were made during listed period, product quality score will be defaulted as 0.01</span></p>
        <table>
        <tbody>
        <tr>
        <td>
        <p><strong>Product</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>Product Quality Score</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>Bid / Click (HKD)</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>Ad Score</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>Ad Ranking</strong></p>
        </td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
        <td>
        <p><strong>A</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>8</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>1</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>8</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>3</strong></p>
        </td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
        <td>
        <p><strong>B</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>6</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>2</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>12</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>2</strong></p>
        </td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
        <td>
        <p><strong>C</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>4</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>3</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>12</strong></p>
        </td>
        <td>
        <p><strong>1</strong></p>
        </td>
        </tr>
        </tbody>
        </table>`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-10',
        question:'Is Boosting subject to other considerations?',
        answer:`However, ads are still subject to other considerations such as Ad score. Only in conditions where two running campaigns are in the same Ad score and are equally relevant to a buyer’s search term will the prioritised Boosting ad be higher bided over the less prominent Boosting ad. For example, if a buyer searches Marketoo Lucky Charm, two Boosting ads with the title Marketoo Lucky Charm will compete for prominence in search results. The higher Product Quality score with higher bids will be shown first.`
    },
    // {
    //     id:'quest-12',
    //     question:'What if I am still unsure of the calculation?',
    //     answer:` If you are still unsure of the calculation, you may refer to our suggested bid value. `
    // },
    {
        id:'quest-11',
        question:'How do you calculate Ads score?',
        answer:`<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ad Score = Max. CPC Bid x Product Quality Score.</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">o </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> In the ad auction mechanism, exposure priority is determined by the total ad score. The total ad score consists of two main factors:</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">o </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">1) With regards to the ad system, product quality scores are just as important as the max. CPC bid. Designers are advised to optimise product pages to improve product quality scores before running ads in order to help listings become more visible to potential customers. Optimised product pages can also help in getting better ad positions. If the quality of the product page is poor, it is not easy to get exposure regardless if you set a high max. CPC bid.</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">o </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">2) Note: When a listing violates Marketoo’s Allowed & Prohibited Items policy and is reported to Marketoo via the “Report this item” function, the system will prohibit the listing from being exposed to users through ad positions.</span></p>`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-12',
        question:'What if I am still unsure about the calculation?',
        answer:`You may refer to our calculator as a reference. Invested amount will only represent estimated ranking and the actual result is based on CTR, conversation rate, product quality score, Ads score and bids from other competitors, etc.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-13',
        question:'How long will my listing stay in Boosting?',
        answer:`Your listing will stay in Boosting for as long as you set your campaign duration to be (3–30 days) and will
        pause for the day once you’ve reached your daily budget (or targeted number of clicks per day). Marking
        your listing as “Sold”, “Out Of Stock”, “Deleted” or changing its category will stop your Boosting
        immediately. Reserved listing's promotion will be paused for a maximum 24 hours. Within 24 hours, listing 
        will bring back the promotion automatically if re-listed product is back to its original state. Over 24 
        hours, then it will be stopped. Re-listing will not cost any surcharge within the duration you paid for.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-14',
        question:'How do I know if my listing is promoted with Boosting?',
        answer:`<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">You may track the clicks and progress of your Boosting campaign through My Ads Performance in“Boosting”</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">1 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">When a user browses a category or search result page, they don’t always tap into all the listings that they see. When they scroll past a listing, it’s counted as an impression. When they tap into the listing to view more details, it’s counted as a click.</span></p>
        <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">2 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">A user has to tap into your Boosting listing for us to count it as a click. On top of that, each click will be unique; if the same user taps into your listing twice on the same day, it will only be counted as 1 click.</span></p>`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-15',
        question:'Does Boosting guarantee a sale?',
        answer:`Boosting provides your listings with more visibility. However, we cannot guarantee that a Boosting will lead to a sale.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-16',
        question:'Can I use a custom keyword to target? ',
        answer:`We all know that buyers search what they want to browse and purchase. As a seller, you would like to put certain keywords in the listing title and description with the hope of being shown in the prominent position for the highly intended keyword. Keyword targeting assures your hope into reality. You can simply type in the keywords you want and your listing will be shown in the keyword search result!`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-17',
        question:'If I choose one keyword for the targeting, does this mean my Boosting ads will only show for that keyword? How it will be charged?',
        answer:`No. Keyword targeting will only give an extra boost to your listing for that keyword search. Your Boosting performance for organic search will not be impacted. Keyword targeting is built for sellers who want more exposure and clicks for a specific keyword. We charge $0.1 bid value per keyword.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-18',
        question:'Can I convert un-used investment back into my original payment method?',
        answer:`You are entitled to advertise products for your listed period and invested amount is non-refundable.`
    },
    // {
    //     id:'quest-19',
    //     question:'Can I add a custom keyword to target?',
    //     answer:`No. The list of the keywords will be automatically generated based on your listing information, and it will be ordered by our recommendation. You can only choose any keyword within the recommended list of keywords.`
    // }
]